It's week eight of me turning $100 into
a million. Last week we took two trades
where one of them made us about $2,000
and then the other we lost $2,000.
Biggest waste of time ever. And now this
week we're going to come and slash the
market. We're going to try and turn
these $20,000
into $40,000.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. It
is week number eight turning $100 into a
million.
And all I can say is that we usually
start Monday morning, very early Monday
morning because Sunday usually nothing
happens.
But not this time. This time is
different. You know what?
I think this is the first time in the
whole entire challenge we start
challenge on a Sunday.
And this might be the Sunday that we
just take a trade on Sunday night and it
can give us the profits for the whole
entire week.
So let's see. Currently right now it is
1:58
in the morning. So it is 2:00 in the
morning
Sunday night, Monday morning. So right
now I'm supposed to be asleep.
But I'm here about to take a trade. So
there's a lot of markets that I am
interested in taking this week, but
50% of these markets are degenerate
markets. Now you guys know what that
means. Degenerate markets means I'm
breaking my trading plan. If I break my
trading plan,
I have to drive the Beetle. Now I
haven't driven the Beetle in about 3
weeks cuz I haven't broken my trading
plan in 3 weeks. But if I break my
trading plan, I am a man of my word. I
will not drive my 3.4 million-dollar
Bugatti to drive the Beetle to show you
guys that you have to hold yourself
accountable every single time you break
a trading plan.
But as of right now we haven't done it.
So let's see if we're about to do it. So
starting off the week is going to be
AUD/USD.
As you guys can see, the degenerate
markets I have Beetle at the top of it
because these are the markets if I do
take this trade, I'm going to have to
drive the [__] Beetle.
Currently right now AUD/USD is at a high
of a resistance. So you can see how we
are a resistance level and resistance
level. So you guys can see here on the
weekly time frame every single time
price comes up into this resistance, one
week rejection. Comes up into this
resistance, one week rejection, and then
hits to the downside. Currently right
now we've had the pull up, the one week
rejection just as it's done here, and we
could anticipate a pullback. We're at a
higher high, so we could anticipate
price to take a pullback to then
continue to head to the upside. Now this
is a countertrend trade because we're
trading against the daily time frame and
the weekly. Daily time frame is still
bullish creating higher high, higher
low, higher high.
But the 4-hour time frame has shifted
bearish. Now we've used this channel in
the past in the last couple of weeks and
it has worked very precisely. Not saying
that we want to use it this week, but
it's just a visual representation. You
guys can see how we were bullish and now
we've broken under that channel. The
structure has gone bearish. This was the
higher low, higher high, broken under.
Now we have a left head kind of right
shoulder going on. And this is literally
exactly where I would want to be
interested in entering this position.
Literally like right Like I can
basically take this trade
right [__] now. Like literally right
now. But
I only like taking positions right at
the beginning of London session,
especially on a Sunday. London session
starts in 1 hour.
But this might have the move before that
as well.
Literally driving me crazy. Because if
you go to the weekly time frame, the
weekly time frame has already created
that wick. So usually what happens is
when the weekly candlestick opens, it
just either has the move, but then it
always has to go back and create the
wick. This is already created the wick,
so it doesn't have to go back up here.
So technically the trade could be ready
to be taken. But I am going to wait for
a little bit more confirmation on this
position. Potentially going to be
another bearish engulfing candlestick so
it's a confirmed rejection from this
area here. US AUD/USD is borderline
about to take. And if I take it,
that means Beetle time or also known as
the Punisher. Next is going to be
USD/JPY, which is not a degenerate
trade. You can clearly see here on the
weekly time frame we are very much
bearish. We were creating higher high,
higher low, higher high, and then we
went bearish, lower high, lower low, and
now we're retesting this weekly
structure level. When you go down to the
daily time frame, you can see here on
the daily time frame this is a very well
respected level of resistance, support,
support, support, resistance,
resistance, support. So whenever we're
above or rejecting, whenever we're
under, we are rejecting. Now
I'm about to show you guys some crazy
voodoo magic [__] And again, this Okay,
obviously it's not [__] voodoo magic,
right? Let's be [__] honest. It's
market structure repetition constantly.
The markets will repeat itself because
these patterns happen time and time
again. This is about to trip you guys
out what I'm about to show you guys. If
you guys like these type of examples and
they make sense to you guys, drop a
comment below so I can keep doing it
because it's a very high level of
analyzation in the markets and it's
almost like Where's Waldo? Like when you
have this big image of Where's Waldo and
once you find them, you almost can't
unsee it. But before you find them, it's
pretty much impossible to find them. But
when you find them, it's very hard to
unsee it. What I'm about to show you
guys right now, you are not seeing it.
As soon as I show it to you, you can't
unsee it. It's going to look super
clear. So let me show you guys. So this
market right here currently is having a
lower high pullback. And this is what
this market structure looks like on this
pullback, right? We have some structure
right here and then we are now at this
resistance level. If I take this same
exact market structure move from right
here and then I simply move it to this
market structure here with the exception
of making this a little bit higher and
aiming this a little bit higher, it's
the exact same move right here, but
instead of it obviously being here, it
is now right here. It's the same exact
move with the exception of it being a
little bit higher. Now what is the
difference?
That this had this [__] the structure up
here and that this one is having it
right here. Let's see what happened here
to see if we can anticipate for it to
happen here cuz we're expecting for the
cells and clearly this one to did this
pattern and then went to the downside.
So let's zoom into this 30 minutes
structure on this circle time frame
right here. What did we get when we were
at this pattern right here?
Oh okay, we got a left head, right
shoulder. Okay, cool. Left head, right
shoulder retest, then sell. Well let's
go to current price right now. Holy
[__] what do we have here? Left head,
right shoulder.
[__] with me. [__] with me. If you want
me to keep showing you guys cuz I see
this all the time and I don't always
explain it because I It's just normal to
me. This is my second language, third
language, and I see this literally every
single day. It's very normal to me. But
to a lot of you guys this might be like
what the [__] or wow moments. And if it
is, let me know in the comments so I can
keep doing this stuff for you guys cuz
it motivates me and it shows me that you
guys are actually learning. So this
position we're actually very, very, very
interested in executing, but not just
yet. I want to execute this position
once we have some type of engulfing
confirmation. So right now I have my
potential entry right under this level
because when this candlestick closes
under it, it is a engulfing candlestick.
So just put my alarm under there to
pretty much notify me once we have that
engulfing candlestick. Even the 15
minute hasn't had the engulfing quite
just yet. So we're going to stay up all
night tonight because that literally
might happen very, very, very soon.
Next is GBP/JPY. So this pair we've been
anticipating it since last week and
currently right now we are at this
resistance level once again. 4-hour time
frame, we're just in this consolidation.
This is very easy. Break retest to then
sell, retest of structure, retest of
EMA, and retest of round psychological
level, 190.500.
Next, AUD/JPY, literally same exact
thing. We're at now this very strong
level of support and resistance all
throughout here. And I'm simply going to
be waiting for price to have a break and
retest under this level to then take
this trade to the downside. Very easy,
very straight to the point. Next,
degenerate trade, Beetle trade. If I
take this trade right here, which I
should not, I will then have to drive
the Beetle. So this was a pair that we
were interested in last week that we
were interested in selling at the retest
of this neckline, but that never
happened and price had to push to the
downside. Now I believe this is going to
be the move that's going to retest the
neckline of GBP/NZD and the head and
shoulders, but I see an opportunity on
that retest. This is the degenerate
trade. You should not be looking to take
this trade. That is a no. You should be
looking to take this sell. But this
countertrend trade does look pretty
decent. We've clearly created a triple
bottom and now we are potentially going
to break out of that area to then take
this trade. The 1-hour time frame is
clearly consolidating and now we're
about to break out of this area along
with the EMA. In order for me to execute
this trade, I'd basically need a break
and a retest and I'd only look for a
very quick short-term buy to just retest
this neckline of the overall head and
shoulders pattern that we have right
here. This is a countertrend trade and
again, when I take a countertrend trade,
I am breaking my trading plan and my
trading rules.
Therefore, if I do that, I have to go
drive the Beetle. But as of right now,
there is no break and no retest. But
we're going to keep our eye on it just
in case if it were to do it. So, this is
the second degenerate trade that if you
were to take it, you would have to drive
the Beetle.
And then lastly, NZDJPY, not even that
focused on it because we have way better
markets that we're going to be
interested in in for this week ahead.
So, I'm going to keep my eye peeled out
on USDJPY
and on AUDUSD.
So,
drum roll.
2:09 in the morning.
See you guys either
in a couple of hours or
tomorrow in the morning.
Set and forget.
All right, guys. So, trade update. It is
currently right now
3:34
in the middle of the night. So, usually
what happens is that I'll start falling
asleep here at the desk. So, I just
literally go take a shower, wakes me up,
and I just come back. So, I just took a
shower right now, and I'm currently
waiting for the market to give me my
entry signal.
Probably going to go for another hour
um to see what the market does.
Nothing's changed. Everything's exactly
the same. Let me show you. USDJPY, still
waiting for the rejection. AUDUSD,
still waiting for the rejection. And the
GBP, still waiting for the break under.
Everything is literally still exactly
the same. GBP NZD has started to have
the break.
So, let's wait for that retest now. But,
I think USDJPY is going to be the first
one that I'm going to be interested in
taking. So, you know, trade update at
3:35. We will see what happens. Thanks.
If not, I'll see you in the morning.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen. Ah.
So, last night we fell asleep at around
4:30, almost 5:00 in the morning. And
that we have just gotten up. It is
currently 9:58 in the morning. So,
Sebastian, my filmmaker, he usually is
here with me, but last night he fell
asleep at 5:00, too.
This guy can't wake up. He can't hang.
Can't hang with the boy. I'm already
used to this whole sleep schedule. I am
fried. So, I can fall asleep at 5:00 and
wake up at 7:00. Like if I slept 6
hours, but I didn't. And I did all that
for nothing. Nothing. The markets
haven't done nothing. This is what I
hate when I put in all this time and I
literally don't catch any trades or have
any high probability trade
opportunities. But, you know what? It's
part of the game. It's part of the risk
to reward of this business. I got to
suck it up. A lot of you guys got to do
that, too. Realize that even if you stay
up and there's nothing happens, don't
feel
timely invested in like, okay, now
because I've been sitting on this chair
for 6 hours, I have to then take a trade
and the market has to give me an
opportunity. No, dude. That is not going
to happen.
So, let me show you guys what I mean.
So, beforehand, you guys can see that
the account currently right now is still
sitting at the same $20,000.
And here the markets, you can see AUDUSD
currently has had the push to the area
of interest just how we wanted to, and
we haven't had the rejection that we've
been looking for. So, we just had that
engulfing about 2 hours ago, which this
is going to pretty much give me my
confirmation that I might be wanting to
enter this trade very, very, very soon.
30-minute time frame, I want to have the
break of this little neckline of the
head and shoulders before I actually
enter this position. So, it can just
confirm that it's rejecting this area of
interest.
Next is GBP NZD. So, we've actually had
the break out of this area. Now, I'm
going to be waiting for the deeper
retest of it in order for us to actually
take this trade to the upside. 4-hour
looks very, very, very, very nice. Just
waiting for the little higher low to now
enter this position to the upside.
USDJPY,
currently literally did nothing. I
thought this was going to be the pair
that we were going to take and it was
going to give us the opportunity, but it
never gave us that rejection engulfing
candlestick that we were looking for,
and it completely avoided this loss to
perfection.
So, for now, I'm not interested in
USDJPY.
GBPJPY, same exact thing. We were
anticipating for price to have a break
and retest under this level, and we
didn't. So, we avoided this loss as
well. And then AUDJPY, waiting for the
break and retest under. We didn't do it.
So, we avoided this loss as well. So,
you guys can see how pretty much some of
the analysis are playing out in our
favor in terms of what we're looking
forward to enter the position, and then
the others just simply didn't. Now, what
do we do in that case? We set and
forget, and we we move on and only focus
on the markets that matter. There's no
need to take a trade in the market that
we are emotionally invested to or timely
invested into it just because we stayed
up all night looking at it. No, we only
take trades that have a high probability
trade setup. And if those trades don't
have a high probability trade setup,
even if we look at it for 30 days, we
simply don't take it. Don't care if it's
your favorite pair. Don't care if your
uh if it's the the pair has the same
letters as your name or if it's a
birthday uh all this superstitious [__]
[__] that. It doesn't matter. What
matters is if it has a high probability
trade. And none of them do. So, let's
see if AUDUSD or GBP NZD give us the
entry signal that we need.
So, once again,
it's currently 10:00 in the morning,
and I will update you guys hopefully
within the hour. All right, guys. Market
update. It is currently 12:17
in the afternoon. So, about 2 and 1/2
hours since the last time we did the
last market update. Patience. Patience.
Patience. I can't describe how much
patience factors in to becoming
successful in trading
because it avoids so many different
losses. I just avoided three losses in
one day because of patience. So, let me
show you right now the trade that we
were interested in taking a couple hours
ago and how we just avoided the loss.
So, AUDUSD, we were interested in taking
this trade as soon as we broke and
retested under it did not break and
retest under the neckline. It created
the right shoulder, but it never
retested and rejected it. So, we did not
take the trade. Patience. Patience.
Patience. This is the key to success
right here. You can't just get FOMO
because you see this pattern right here
and you feel like you have to get in
because it's going to have the push. If
it has the push, phenomenal. Great.
That's what you want cuz it's going to
confirm to you that the move is actually
happening. You just wait for a little
pullback to then enter. But, you can't
get FOMO just because you see the
pattern. Because the pattern happens, it
doesn't mean that it has to have the
move. So, we avoided that loss to
perfection. I I'm still very much
interested in it. I just have to wait
for now this market to have a better
rejection from this area of interest.
And then GBP NZD, we are still waiting
for price to have the retest of this
structure level to take the trade to the
upside.
Oh.
Look who's back. Huh?
I'm doing trade updates by myself. Huh?
Thanks for coming back to work.
No. You don't get one of those until you
have been here all week. I've been doing
this by myself.
Holding the camera like this sucks.
So, we finally have Salas back. He
decided to come back to work. Welcome
back, brother. Decided to wake up. Yeah.
The literally, it is right now 12:57 at
night. Pretty much about to be 1:00 in
the morning. Trade update. The market
has played out. Drum roll, please.
We got a pump at the gym today. Can you
tell?
One of these days I'm going to get a
cramp, bro. That's going to suck.
But, I'm going to hit the gym, and the
market has moved exactly how we've been
anticipating. So,
earlier on AUDUSD,
we were anticipating for price to have a
break of this neckline right here. I was
showing you guys on the 30-minute time
frame.
The market did have the break, but I was
waiting for the retest. Did not have the
retest, and I [__] missed the whole
entire move. But, I do believe that this
market could have a pullback now in
London session, and then in New York,
it's going to have the push again. It's
having the move very early on into the
session, and I feel like it's not just
done yet. I feel like this is going to
wick back up on the daily time frame.
Feel like the 1-hour time frame has to
create that lower high. It's going to
give us that beautiful entry to then
head to the downside. GBPNZD never had
the retest how we wanted it. So, price
literally just went straight to the
upside. Good thing we avoided this trade
right here because honestly,
I did not want to drive the Beetle. So,
this trade made us avoid taking the
trade on the Beetle.
Fantastic. Because now what we can do is
put the money at risk on the real
position. So, we avoided taking this
countertrend trade, and now we're going
to look for the retest of the cells of
this neckline of the head and shoulders.
Next is USDJPY. Currently, you guys can
see that we're having some type of
reaction, but we're having it at the top
of this level of support and resistance.
The only way that I would be interested
in this position is once and if we
decide to have a break and retest of
this level to then head to the downside.
Daily time frame closed very strongly
bullish, and the daily time frame is now
bullish because we've broken above here.
The least that I can ask for on this
position is for the 4-hour to go bearish
in order for us to be interested in this
trade. Same thing with GBPJPY. We've had
a push to the upside, daily creating
above the level of support and
resistance throughout here. Very strong
resistance, very strong support. We've
closed above, so it could retest and
head to the upside.
So, not that interested. And lastly,
AUDJPY, same exact thing. Broke above
the resistance, using it as support.
Right now, we can potentially head to
the upside. Now, what I'm going to be
waiting for on this is the same thing.
A break and retest under. So, the main
pair that is about to be ready to enter
is AUDUSD, like I said, and it had the
[__] move. We just missed it. Now,
I'm just going to wait for this trade to
have the pullback to enter the trade.
And GBPNZD, a rejection to then sell.
Looks like it's going to be another
really long night.
Don't fall asleep today, [__]
I don't want to rest, so all right,
we're good.
Stay tuned.
Don't miss another trade, [__]
Drum roll, please.
For the [__] trade update.
19,000
[__] dollars in profit. Now,
What? How fast did this happen?
Very fast. Let me show you guys. So,
right now, USD/JPY, exactly how I
explained yesterday. We literally
explained the only way we'd be
interested in taking this position right
here is if we have a break, retest, and
then sell. Price literally broke,
retested, sell. Exactly what we
anticipated, perfect entry signal,
literally 1 hour ago, as you guys can
see down here. 8:00 in the morning.
Currently right now, it is 10:00 in the
morning. So, as soon as we entered this
position, market immediately started
heading to the downside. Look how fast
this momentum of this market is
currently moving. Beautiful 30-minute
bearish engulfing evening star
formation. 15-minute time frame, as soon
as the candlestick closed, boom, just
completely downside move, which is
absolutely beautiful. This is the trade
that we avoided
yesterday, and we avoided to take the
loss cuz it never retested and gave us
the engulfing of this left head and the
right shoulder. Now, avoided this loss,
we can remove this.
Now, we have this position right here.
Which is looking decent, right?
Obviously, I'm just hyped because I
risked a lot more than I should have
because we're trying to turn 20,000
dollars into 40. So, I can literally
close the position right now, and then
we will have the 40,000 dollars in
profit that we need. Literally.
OH. OH, [__] OH, OH, OH, WHAT? OH,
[__] What the [__] just happened?
Oh, [__] Oh, oh.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't you [__] quit.
Hold on, I'm in the I'm in shock right
now. Yo, I saw 50,000. It was It was at
the bottom of that wick right there. Are
is news happening right now? Probably.
Well, now I'm on edge. I'm going to put
an alarm right around my entry signal
just to let me know that it is up there.
I have to put a an alarm at the bottom
of this candlestick. If we If we get a
candlestick to go back under that
wick, we're pretty much good. We are
good.
Okay.
You don't You don't want this.
All right. So, currently right now, we
had a little quick uh spasm in the
markets. This is what trading in the
market is. This is why people go crazy
when they risk more money than they
should. If I was risking, you know, 3,
4, 5% like a normal human, I wouldn't
even care.
Oh.
Right now, 40,000 dollars floating in
profit. That's it. All we care about.
Next, AUD/USD.
So, yesterday we anticipated after this
lower low that we were going to have a
lower high pullback to retest the
structure level and then the EMA to head
to the downside. Price did not do that,
so we clearly did not enter this
position. GBP/CHF.
Oh, [__] Look at this beautiful trade.
So, we have pulled up to the area of
interest of the head and shoulders time
frame, exactly how we've been
anticipating, and we are officially
having our reaction candlestick from
this area. Now, if you go down to the
1-hour, you can very clearly see how we
shifted the structure right here. We
went from higher high, higher low,
higher high to now lower low. This is
great, phenomenal, amazing, perfecto
fino. Now, what we have to do is wait
for a lower high to then sell this
position, just exactly how we did here.
Lower low, lower high, engulfing, sell.
Lower low, need the lower high,
engulfing,
and then sell. So, this is exactly what
we did here. We had the lower low, lower
high, engulfing,
and then sell.
You guys are seeing the [__] pattern
here? It's literally the same [__] every
single time.
This [__] got This [__] got me hyped
right now. We we we can't even look at
it. We can't. It's going to [__] with
us.
We got to just set it and forget. If
this trade hits down here, you know
we'll be like at 150,000, right? You
understand that? Do you have that clear?
This candlestick just opened, and it did
And yes, there was definitely news. Let
me actually go check if there was news.
Okay, there you go. So, we actually did
have news right now at 10:00 a.m.
Tuesday, September 3rd, 10:00 in the
morning, USD red flag, ISM
manufacturing, blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah.
Clearly, you can see how fundamentals
always follow technicals. This is the
perfect example of it. Obviously, it's
going to have a little spasm like
but the overall move is going to follow
the technical analysis of it.
So, for now, last market update right
now
at 10:04 in the morning. Though, the
last update right now at 10:05 in the
morning is going to be 25,000 dollars in
profit.
Set it and forget it.
So, by the way, yes, this is a real
weapon. It's never been loaded before.
It's never been used. I kind of just
like it for decoration. This [__] was
5,000 dollars. Gold-plated Colt 45, you
know, I just
feel like a
feel like a narc with this [__] you
know? So,
trade update, right? It's kind of
annoying because every single [__]
trade that I predict, I've been I've
been predicting them. I've just been so
selective about it, which is good, but
it's also bad cuz I'm getting a little
bit of a
fear inside of me. But, I'm a man. I got
this, and I got to lead by example when
I'm showing you guys. This is part of
the journey of the 100 to the mill. We
started off good, not giving a [__] and
now I'm at the point where I'm giving
too much of a [__] cuz I don't want to
blow the account. But, I got to get to
remove that mindset to limit the beliefs
so I can continue to scale the account.
Trying to get this across to you guys,
right? So, trade update right now, the
account is currently at 3,400
dollars, and you guys can see that the
position is actively pulling back
further than we anticipated, and I
actually want the 4-hour to close like
this. I want it to close a very strong
doji because in the next candlestick
should fill that very, very, very well.
The 1-hour just closed right now along
with the 30 minutes as as a nice
30-minute doji. If this next candlestick
could have this right here,
beautiful, amazing. We we We need that.
Cuz this would be a literally the same
pattern as right here to then continue
selling to the downside. But, I might
close this position out to then
potentially enter GBP/NZD because this
is the one that it's actually retesting
the daily neckline of the head and
shoulders a lot cleaner. It's retesting
and rejecting the EMA, the round
psychological level. This trade just
overall looks a lot better, and I might
just remove the liability from the other
pair and just transfer it to this one.
So, I'm going to be waiting for the
pullback and some rejections here, and
then there I'll determine the decision
that I make. And it's so annoying
because we've been calling this position
since yesterday. We never got the
pullback, and the trade has been moving
[__] beautifully. But, it is what it
is. We're going to continue to monitor
this trade literally every single tick.
Like, I'm here on the 15-minute time
frame watching every single tick because
if this position comes into Like, look
where I have my alarm. I had a I have
alarms set up 1.46009.
That's about the 30-minute EMA, 1-hour
EMA. If it gets there, I think it could
just continue breaking to the upside.
So, if it gets there, I'm just going to
close my losses there,
and then just move on to the next one.
Cuz I'm not Like, at this point in the
challenge, if the position from right
away doesn't go straight into profit and
just stays there, I am going to simply
cut my losses. But, if the position goes
straight into a loss, I can't do
anything about it. But, if the position
goes from a winning position to then up
to a losing one, I'd be dumb to not
close it out. If it was a regular trade,
I wouldn't give a [__] But, since we're
in the challenge, I have to be very
strategic because clearly the trade
might not go in the direction that I am
anticipating. A trade is supposed to go
from the moment you enter it straight
into your take profit or straight into
your stop loss. But, if it goes in
between and it starts going back Like,
it doesn't hit your take profit and then
it starts going back up into your stop
loss, well, the trade might just
reverse. Be a you know, be a step ahead
and close it out half the loss. So,
we're analyzing that as we go. So, stay
tuned.
Today, we're going to pay a stranger's
rent.
I'm guessing the rent can be
1,200 bucks.
How How much more or less do you guys
pay for rent in this area? What would
you guys say?
Let me Okay. One One second.
Wait, one second.
And we always get by. Yeah, it's for you
guys.
I What else can I do for you guys? Is
there anything else I can help you guys
out with?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
the risk if the trade were to reverse
from here and go back into my entry. I'm
not going to give a [__] because I
accept the risk. I am a firm believer
that this trade has a lot more downside
potential than just this move right
here.
So you know what I'm going to do?
Right here. I don't think they're ready.
So we're going to [__] set and
forget.
We'll check back in later. See you guys.
Drum roll, please. Drum roll,
please.
Market [__] update. 65
[__] dollars.
Ah. Oh.
Oh, no.
Oh, there you go.
65,000
[__] dollars in profit in the
account. The highest we have been. Why?
Because we set and forget.
Set and forget. Now, you guys can
clearly see here on the TradingView.
Yesterday, we were borderline [__] We
almost went straight into our drawdown
where I would have closed out the
position and this trade would have went
straight into profit. Yesterday, we had
a lower low and I'm like, all right,
cool. Now we have a lower high. This is
a good spot to sell. New lower low. Now
we're having a new lower high for a new
potential lower low, which in three
[__] minutes, if it closes like this,
boys,
it's sales to the bottom. Sales to the
bottom. Is that even a [__] thing? I
guess it is now. I guess it is now. Cuz
we can make anything we want now.
We can I can make up a word called bra.
All right, so this market is looking
really [__] good right now, dude.
I would love for the next 3 minutes for
this candlestick to body candlestick
close under this point right here. So
even on the 30-minute time frame, we
create a new lower low. If we create a
new lower low, then this can pretty much
be confirmed to continue to head to the
downside. But I might want to close the
position right then and there because we
are approaching this level of structure
here and price could have some type of
reaction to then the upside, but I do
think overall we could continue heading
to the downside. I just can personally
see this maybe having a little
retracement and then moving down.
And honestly, I don't want to be part of
that. I just want to get my profits and
bounce. So within the next 2 and 1/2
minutes,
we're going to find out. And in those 2
and 1/2 minutes, I'll just be updating
you guys on these other markets. So
AUD/USD,
we had the take profit pretty much hit
perfectly where we were looking to enter
this trade and then exit this position
right around here. So price had to move
perfectly.
AUD/JPY
had the break how I was pretty much
anticipating, but now we're having the
retest and now we can potentially enter
position cuz you guys got to keep in
mind, dude, it is literally
Wednesday.
I can close out this position right now
and I can still catch another position
and turn the stack with that 65,000. I
can still turn that to 120 this same
week. I don't have to, but if there's
great opportunities, I'm going to do it.
So this is literally
a perfect example of that. This has had
a beautiful daily body candlestick
closure under. Now we can have a quick
lower high to then continue heading to
the downside. GBP/NZD,
this this this this this John right here
is loading up. If this daily candlestick
closes as a doji, the next day is going
to be a very strong move. That's it.
Done. Done. It's just going to happen.
[__] it. Done setting possible
scenarios. It's just going to happen
because I said so.
That's just how [__] works nowadays.
USD/JPY,
no, GBP/JPY
has had the break. Now it's having a
little [__] retest, so we're going
to be waiting on that. NZD/JPY,
bra.
And then this one, bra. So basically,
our only market that we're looking at
right now is USD/JPY
to see what we're about to do right now
and GBP/NZD for a little break and
retest to then sell and
AUD/JPY for a quick retest to sell. So
USD/JPY, we got 30 seconds right now.
33. Let's just Let's just do this
together, right? Let's have this
countdown together.
So we have here
66,000 dollars and let's go on the
30-minute time frame so we can see if
it's going to close on the You know
what? Want to know what would suck so
bad? If right now that [__] just
That would suck so so bad.
All right, come on.
9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1.
Oh, [__] OH MY GOD.
OH, [__]
YO,
YO.
NO. YO.
YO, I CAN'T YO, I CAN'T MAKE THIS UP,
DUDE. YO, I CAN'T MAKE THIS UP, DUDE.
HOLY HOLY [__]
HOLY [__]
BRO.
YO, IT'S NOT STOPPING,
DUDE. OH MY GOD, 100,000. YO, THERE'S NO
WAY.
YO, THERE'S NO WAY.
YO. YO, THERE'S NO THERE'S NO WAY. OH, I
kind of hurt myself.
Is my watch okay?
Yeah, it's fine. Doesn't matter. We can
buy another one.
Oh. Oh. OH, DUDE. OH.
YO, WE'RE ABOUT TO BE AT 100,000. That's
[__] crazy.
Yo, the countdown is legendary.
YO.
NO, NO, NO, NO. WE GOT TO KEEP GOING. WE
GOT TO KEEP GOING.
We got to keep going. We got to keep
going.
95.
95. Oh, 97. Yo, it's going to hit
100,000. Yo, it's going to hit 100,000.
We got to keep going.
Look, dude, I I think I think we got up
to like
Dude, did we get up to there?
Now I just got to focus.
What is it on?
Why didn't do this?
This right here shows you guys that the
[__]
fundamentals will follow the technicals.
All right, I got to focus, dude. Market
update, boys. Markets update, boys.
And ladies and gentlemen, we have
officially
officially closed the account at No, no,
no. Drum roll, please.
Thank you very much.
We have officially closed at 90,000
[__] dollars on the account. Now,
not going to lie, we were a little bit
impulsive. I can't even lie. I was
literally looking at this and I was
contemplating do I close, do I hold, do
I hold, do I close, do I close, do I
hold? And usually what happens when you
spike like that happens is it'll come
into here and then it'll wick. It'll
create a ginormous wick. And you know
what? I said [__] that. I don't want to,
you know, risk that. So, I ended up
closing the position somewhere around
maybe right around here. So, if I would
have literally just waited for the
candlestick to close, I would have
literally gotten a lot more profit
because the price ended up going all the
way down here. If I would have kept the
hold down there, I would have easily
easily gotten
106,110,000
dollars. But, you know what?
I am very content. I am very I'm more
than satisfied. We've doubled the goal
for the week because the goal for the
week was to turn 20 to 40. Dude, between
20 to 90. So, the goal for next week, we
have just done it this [__] week
right now. I was literally just telling
you guys I we closed right now at
60,000, I can maybe turn it into 120
this week. Dude, we just got so much
closer to that goal right now. If you
would have closed at 40 or 50, like
we're already there on this one week.
And it's only
Wednesday.
It is literally Wednesday at 12:00. We
still have a whole 2 and 1/2 days of
good market movement. So, for now, I'm
going to continue to set and forget this
trade. And I'm going to stay interested
on GBP NZD to continue sells to the
downside, break and retest to the
downside. AUD/JPY is literally having
the reaction exactly how I explained.
We're having the reaction from this
level of support and resistance to the
downside. So, I'm not going to chase
this. I'm just going to wait to see if
it gives me a better entry. And GBP/JPY,
going to see if it gives me a better
entry.
Boys,
dude, we're
Make sure all my things are good, you
know.
Boys,
all I can say is
[__] set and forget. So, now you guys
may ask, Alex, what do you do after a
day like this? What do you do? Honestly,
nothing. I literally just chill It's
just another boring day. But, today is a
bit different. Coincidentally enough
that we had a crazy trade like this,
we're going to go look at new houses.
So, I might move into a new house
probably in the next month or two
because I like moving every year, paying
more in rent because it just opens my
mind more, forces me to make more money.
And um I don't know to move to another
house, to a a penthouse. So, come with
us to go tour these different apartments
and houses to see where we're going to
go to. We're actually late. So,
let's go.
Um I mean, look at it. Dude, literally I
literally felt like I was in Scarface
walking through this house, bro.
They for sure
assassinate somebody in this house, no
doubt.
And they for sure move drugs, no doubt.
I mean, you look like you'd do the same
thing. No, I'm a trader, bro.
What do What did you think?
Look at it. Look at this.
I
I honestly thought the same thing, but
we we're going to have to sacrifice a
lot.
Yo, bro, there's no parking No parking
down there.
I like my house right now. Like if I can
put my house there, perfect. Done.
[__]
How much does that one go for a month?
That one's going for 45,000 dollars a
month. That's [__] Yeah. Full time
minimum wage an hour. I know. But, like
it's like the cheapest one in this whole
island. Just Not Not because I'm looking
for the cheapest one, it's because
there's just nothing other Like there's
nothing else available. Like look at
this house. Do you think somebody that
owns this house is going to ever sell
it? No. Look at that. He has a pond in
front of his house. Like this guy's
never going to sell that house. Like
these guys hit the gold mine and then
they just stick on it. The people that
buy these houses are rich. They don't
ever want to rent it out. If I were to
buy one of these houses, I would never
want to rent it out. So, the only ones
that are still available are these
little shitty ones right here. Like
these little shitty ones are the only
ones that are available. You have to buy
it,
demolish it, and then construct it into
something like this.
And there's literally only probably 15,
20 homes in this whole entire island
left for that type of opportunity
because they're all built up like this.
They literally are already being
demolished and they're already
fixing it up. Look, there's workers 24/7
fixing them up.
There's really any ones on there. So,
right now we're going to go to the
Flatiron again to go view the biggest
and craziest penthouse in all of Miami.
Going for 60,000 dollars a month. And
then we're going to go to the brand new
building Aston Martin. We're going to go
check out the third biggest unit in the
whole entire building. So,
I don't know. We're going to make a
decision.
You know, first or last.
Second,
if you I honestly
Second place is the first loser. Always.
Always remember that.
And third place is the biggest loser.
And third place, dude, who remembers the
guy in third place? Think about that.
Some people might remember you in
second, but they're like, ah, he didn't
get first.
It's about to be the biggest It should
be good.
Like look at this.
Like it goes way that way.
And then it's half the second floor and
then the third floor rooftop.
And the 60,000 a month is [__] crazy,
dude.
Like it's it is, but but but it isn't.
Like
No, but the trade that you made today,
you can [__] basically pay for it.
Yeah, but I traded almost his stop loss.
Um cuz for me it's just it's burnt cash.
You get me? It's literally money just
being like GT3RS.
Never mind GT3.
Um it's just burnt, dude. Like I
literally just
Pixie Dust gone forever.
60K a month. That's like some That is
like somebody that went to college,
studied for 4 years,
works overtime,
that's their salary, 60K a year. And I'm
just paying it on rent.
Bro, the disrespect uh towards money is
crazy. It just shows you guys that
money's not real.
It's not.
You just
click a couple buttons and make that
money. It's not real. You don't have to
work for it. You don't have to literally
like do labor work to get that money
back.
Just use your [__] brain.
Now we're going to go see the Aston
Martin. It's that one right there.
So, this unit is literally the newest
and most prestige unit in all of Miami
right now.
The only thing I don't like is not as
much as in the city. It's like, dude,
like if we're going to be in the city,
we're going to be in the city. But, I
don't want to be half-assed in the city.
They just sold the
main penthouse or the second main
penthouse for 25 million. The unit that
you we were just at was a 20 million
dollar unit. That's what they're selling
at. So, they they either sell it for 20
million or rent it for 60,000.
And then here I come
being like a dumbass and renting it.
Yeah, I'll pay your mortgage. Here,
let's go. I'll do it.
All right. So, Aston Martin, sick
amenities, can't even lie. Definitely
one of the best amenities I've ever
seen. I mean, what would you expect?
It's a brand new building, 2024, 2025.
But, it literally looks like a JV
version of the unit that we just saw. I
feel like such a [__] if I were to get
that. And they're worth the same price.
One is worth Well, technically this one
they're listing it for like 50,000, the
other one 60, but you know, I got that
Alex G negotiation. I get [__] done.
But,
no, like my standards are so [__] up
after looking at that other unit, bro.
Like what what do you think?
We just have to do the other unit, bro.
Three floors versus one floor. Mhm.
And it's literally the highest building
in that area versus here on the other
side of the Yeah, there's those of the
house we have like buildings.
Yeah, that's super cringe in my opinion.
And you walk in and the first thing you
see is the master bedroom. Yeah. What
the [__]
that honestly didn't make sense.
Yeah, that was really weird.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Whoa.
Didn't see you there. How are my acting
skills?
All right.
So, I'm not mad, but trade update, I'm
not mad, but
I would say emotions got to me. I'm
going to explain to you guys why. So,
just to show you guys currently right
now, it is 8:00 at night. So, I just got
back home about an hour ago from
viewing the houses and penthouses. You
guys can see the account is currently at
90,000. So, we haven't obviously done
anything since we closed it. But, look
at the position. Look at this [__] So,
the position was literally creating that
big push to the downside to continue
going to the downside. So,
I closed here on emotion because the
market had obviously the big push at
that moment and I was just seeing more
numbers than I should have, but I [__]
up because I literally was not
practicing what I preach, which is
watch the charts, not the numbers. I was
literally watching the numbers and I got
lost because I saw something close to
100,000. Like if that matters.
Obviously, it matters for the challenge,
but it doesn't matter for the charts.
So, this chart, whatever it's doing
right here is going to directly reflect
on the MetaTrader. So, if I would have
just continued to set and forget this
position right now, we would be up a one
to six risk to reward where we pretty
much closed out at Let's just say one to
four. So, So, could have gotten an extra
two risk to reward on this position.
Meaning, we could have been right now
floating in profit about
to 150,000.
I'm not mad, right? I I I don't care,
but I am acknowledging the fact that I
did get emotional in that very moment. I
was super hyped and I was scared of
losing the money and giving it back to
the markets. I can guarantee you if this
would have been a regular position that
I was taking outside of the challenge, I
would have probably continued to hold
the position simply because the
technicals still indicate that price is
going to continue heading to the
downside.
So, I was emotionally invested into the
position and the
the fact that I continued to hold
throughout two days of it going from
break even to then having the position
to go back is already strong. Now, to
hold after news fundamental like that, I
just
I just couldn't handle it. I just wanted
to get my profits for the week and then
done. So, that's also another reason I
surpassed the goal for the week. I'm not
I'm not greedy, but I am acknowledging
that I did get emotional and I'm not
going to let that happen to me during
now throughout the challenge because,
boys,
we're getting close. It's feeling just
like the It's feeling just like when I
was reaching the 2 300k on the last 100
to the mill.
[__] starts coming up faster. Haters are
not coming up faster talking [__]
making some [__] up. It's all It's
all happening again. It's like It's
literally what I said. When I turn $100
to 200, no one cares. When I turn 200 to
400, no one cares. When I turn 400 to
800, no one cares. Oh, but when I start
making more money in one day that they
make in their whole entire year, oh, now
they're pissed off. Well, boys,
you're about to get so mad cuz I'm going
to do this. I'm going to turn the
[__] $100 into a mill whether you
like it or not. Simple. So,
this right here would have put us a
bigger step forward into that challenge,
but sadly, it
has not because we closed the position
out earlier, which is fine. It is still
currently right now Wednesday. So, we
still have Thursday and Friday. So, we
still have two good days of the markets.
AUD/USD is currently having a push to
the upside, which we're not really
interested in it. AUD/JPY
had the retest exactly how I anticipated
and then had the push exactly how I
anticipated, which is,
you know, not ideal. We can potentially
wait for another bigger pullback on the
daily to then enter the sell to the
downside, which would then create a
4-hour double top retest of this area to
then head to the downside. GBP/NZD
is
not having the shift of structure how we
wanted it to, so we simply are not
interested in this trade. USD/JPY, for
me the trade is done. I am not
interested in looking at this position
anymore. I don't want to add positions.
I don't want to scale in. I don't want
to add not nothing. The trade is done.
Whenever I win a trade, that's it. I
don't want to look at it. I don't want
to deal with it. I don't want to get
involved in it because any decision that
I'm going to make on this trade right
now will have some type of influence on
me thinking that I can predict
everything that this market can do
simply because I just caught a winning
trade. So, when I win a trade, as soon
as it hits my take profit, I like to
stop looking at it. I just don't want to
trade anymore. I want to find the same
opportunity that I took, I just a
different market. It's kind of like when
you take those other kind of trades.
Like once you take the trade and you hit
take profit,
you bounce. You don't stick around. You
don't keep watching. Dude, you bounce.
And you don't ever take the same trade
two times in one day. Never make that
mistake,
gentlemen.
And ladies. All right, fine.
You don't
Bro, I could have been a comedian, dude.
So, when you take the trade and it hits
take profit,
you bounce. You set and forget that
[__] You look for another trade.
So, we're not interested in this trade
anymore. So, now we move on to then
GBP/JPY,
where we are then waiting for this to
come back and retest. Had the retest how
I wanted to, but we were obviously in
USD/JPY. So, we're now going to wait for
a retest in here to then sell.
And then NZD/JPY, same exact thing.
We've had the break. Now, we're looking
for the retest to then pretty much sell.
So, oh, and GBP/CHF, [__] this. Don't
even care about it.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's been good
day, long day. I'm not going to go hit
the gym.
And then let's see where the day takes
us.
So, set and forget. So, set and forget.
Trade up.
Trade up there.
No trades as of right now.
No trades as of right now. Remember,
that is the market. When you see that,
you see the market.
When you
take a loss, you take it out on the
market.
When you take a win, you take it out on
the market.
So, get a figure in your office in your
space and label it as the market so you
can
take care of
Right now, trade update, we are
currently up
850,000.
No, I'm kidding. The day will come
though when I do say a trade update just
like that.
Count right now is still currently at
90,000. We will be up that amount soon.
Trust me.
So, as of right now, we are currently
looking at GBP/NZD.
Actually, before that,
let's just take a second to admire the
set and forget strategy playing out to
perfection by following the trend with
the trade. This trade, if we would have
continued to set and forget, would have
given us overall one to seven risk to
reward, doubling our profit. We would
have been at about $170,000 in the
account. But, let's just pretend like
that didn't even happen anymore. Let's
go to now a new trading opportunity that
we're interested in trading. GBP/NZD.
Yesterday, we had a retest of the
neckline of the head and shoulders,
daily doji, and rejection from the EMA
and round psychological level, 2.1200.
Then here on the 4-hour, we are
currently not having a beautiful shift
structure. And this shift of structure
is a clear higher high, higher low,
higher high, higher low, higher high
shift of structure. You want to count
this as the lower high, blah blah blah,
we shifted. You want to count this as
the lower high, still bearish. But,
the 1-hour looks beautiful. Why? Well,
because we have a left head, right
shoulder retest from that neckline,
retest of
round psychological level 2.1200.
And now the 30-minute is having that
rejection engulfing candlestick that
we're looking for. We have the shift of
structure. 15-minute is bullish.
30-minute is still bearish. This is not
a bad trade at all to take right now.
Like if I were to take this position, it
could be something like this.
My stop loss could be somewhere right
around here for about 40 pips. And then
my first take profit, let's just say we
label it at this area right here. This
can be a quick one to three risk to
reward. Now, the only thing I don't like
is that it is currently Thursday. So,
since it's currently Thursday, we
basically have about
We have less than 24 hours in this
trade.
Because this trade, we take it right
now, we have to let all of the rest of
New York session, which is not much.
Currently right now, it is 11:40 in the
morning. It's a bit late. So, there's
not much volume left in the markets.
We're pretty much betting on
the London session of tonight
and
a little bit of the New York session
tomorrow. Which truthfully, if you just
look at the weekly candlestick, you have
to ask yourself,
what are the odds of this weekly
candlestick now having a wick rejection
to the downside within the next 24
hours?
Probably not that high. If you go to the
daily time frame, you got to ask
yourself, what are the probabilities of
this having the full rejection that we
want in 24 hours?
Probably not that high. What this is
probably going to create now is this
daily doji as well or maybe like another
little red engulfing candlestick like
this rejecting the area. And then the
next day will have the pullback, which
this could be a trade that we could be
very interested in taking come Monday or
Sunday night. So, just taking a little
bit over on the analysis on this market.
These are all things that, you know,
once you're an experienced trader, you
just start looking into an all different
types of angles and it just starts all
making sense cuz at the end of the day,
you got to ask yourselves, yo, what
makes more sense? Take it now or take it
Monday? Well, why take it now? Why take
it Monday? You build the scenario like
this and it it it it almost just
makes sense right away. So,
yeah, we'll update you guys on these
markets.
Right now, it is 12:00 on Thursday.
Today, let's see where the day takes us.
SO, TODAY,
SO, GUYS, JUST THE THINGS RIGHT NOW
WHERE WE'RE going to
get some gearing
and get ready for bumper cars.
So, today we have some special guest
with our bumper car challenge.
We have Neil, Jack Doherty,
Billy and Barbara. We're about to get
some helmets, mouthpieces.
Make sure the boys are protected. It
reminds me of the Super Bowl.
Okay, so, if if you were to like
potentially be in like a a legend of a
vehicle,
which one would you want to wear?
Probably that one.
Black one on the bottom. This one, the
black one on the bottom?
Okay. Can you try it on? Let me see how
it looks on you. No.
I think so. Come on.
You know who I am? Yes, bro. I mean you
were doing
Would you Would you think this would
work? Yes. All right, try it on.
Camp pillow. Oh, yeah. This This might
do the job.
Try that on.
You want to take a punch? Yeah?
Don't miss. How hard? Don't miss. I can
I can hit it hard though. Don't miss.
All right, so this guy is using a
pillow. Yeah.
How long have you had this pillow?
There you go. You good?
All right, I feel like that's not going
to do anything. Can you try these on?
Hold.
Thank you.
And I'm proud to be
in a collision No, it won't work. Yeah.
Something won't get in your eye. You got
protection, man. It's better than no
protection. All right, we'll take it. We
need five We need five of them. Look at
how you look, dude.
I think I'm ready.
You're making a mark in history right
now. We don't need that. Okay.
We don't
We don't litter. We don't We're good for
the environment.
[__]
The experience I'll I'll I'll take
blame. I was late. The cars were
whatever. We're going to do it again.
But like double the size bigger. We're
going to have ramps and obstacles and
[__] Then give us like 2 or 3 days
notice so we can invite more people.
Okay, but you guys will pull up again.
You actually get in the car? Yes, I'll
do it next time.
You got my word.
And take off the [__] airbags. Okay,
but you'll pull up again.
But the airbag blew like the windshields
should be gutted.
Even the windows.
Nah, the windows is good. I'm going to
take this mouth and mold it. I'm going
to I'm going to bring a helmet. You'll
bring it back. And I'm crashing in your
ass and we're good.
That's how I get hurt.
They do all that and then I throw one
rock and it bounces off.
Guys, I don't know if you know but
I can I used to pitch like a like a 90.
Yo, watch out, BRO. YO, WAIT. WATCH OUT.
YO, WATCH OUT. WATCH OUT.
I USED TO YEAH, I USED TO PITCH A WHILE
AGO.
OH, that was a long shot. That was nice.
All right, let's see a lefty lefty
lefty.
I guess
He's excited.
He's like
Yo, we
We're in the danger zone right now. Yo,
wait. Heads up.
Watch out.
That's our front windshield. That's a
custom.
What is that?
Watch out. Watch out.
Don't be shooting [__] out here, dog.
That's a bad idea.
[__] said
That [__] this [__]
No.
I I feel bad I did that.
Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
Oh, [__]
YOU GUYS SEE ME CRASHING IN THE
BUILDING, BRO?
DUDE, I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING. I ran out
of gas.
I think we're going to [__] die where
we go.
You can do the honors.
That's it?
What the [__] is that? Oh, [__] All
right, trade update. So, you guys can
see here AUDUSD
currently had a ginormous push to the
downside on Oh, [__] Damn, that would
have sucked if you were to have taken
that position.
GBP NZD would have been a major major L.
Look, dude. I had the podcast right now.
GBPJPY
No, USDJPY.
Bro, if you would have continued to hold
this position right here, we would have
literally literally probably turned
these same $90,000 to about
like 150. Right now, we are currently at
$90,000 on the account. And um
Actually, let's go upstairs so I can
give you the better trade update right
now.
I can't I can't explain. There's a
surprise coming. That's why.
What surprise is coming, dude? I don't
know. He's a little slow. But he's not
supposed to be slow.
This guy, bro.
Yo, stop this dude. Yo, you did
Bro, congrats on [__] racing, dude.
Hey, bro. I was going to get a 48 and
then Bro, when did you do it? What the
[__] Uh last week.
Last week? How the [__] did I know,
dude?
Nah, I was going to surprise you, bro.
Yeah, we look Bro, I was going to get a
48 and then that down was like 90k so I
was like [__] that. Nah, [__] that.
So, congrats, bro.
Yo, you think you can you can you can
you can drift for sure, though?
Bro, that'd be gangster.
Bro, you got to do it. You got it? Yo,
bro. We got to do it 100%. I'll help
you.
Worst case, I just hold the steering
wheel.
Yo, congrats, bro.
Yo, bro. It's stupid gangster. Hello, it
shoots flames. It shoots flames? Yeah,
yeah.
It's like 900 horsepower.
900 horsepower? More than [__]
God.
Bro.
Gangster.
Are these seats comfortable or no,
right?
Yeah, they actually really are, bro.
Yeah?
Okay, when I when I finish this meeting
right now, I'll pull up on you. Let me
finish this [__] real quick and I'll
pull up.
Got it. I'll see you. Got it. Yeah. We
got to look. All right.
Congrats, bro.
God, what a savage, bro. What a savage.
So, he's like I want to do the trade
update outside. Like bro, we never do
trade updates outside. Trade update,
huh? Sneaky [__] huh? That was
uh sus. I was like, dude, we do trade
updates in the computer. We don't do
trade updates outside. He's like, no, we
have to. I'm like, okay, now it makes
sense. By the way, that's crazy because
like Jordan can't even walk right now.
And the fact that he traded his R8 and
you guys have seen Jordan. He's been
popping in and out throughout the whole
entire series. He's currently battling
cancer. And the fact that he cannot walk
and he just bought himself a brand new
600LT shows you guys that he's doing
whatever he can to shift his mindset to
getting better so he could drive the
car. He loves cars. So, he wants to
drive the car. Now, what is he going to
do? He's going to put himself in a
situation where he has to force himself
to get better so he can then drive the
car. So, I don't know, man. I think
that's like super inspirational and
the [__] that he's going through is
ridiculous, bro. He's been battling this
now for like 2 or 3 years. Then he's
doing chemo now and stuff. So,
shout out to Jordan. We're going to pull
up on him tonight. Maybe we get some
clips of that. If not, we'll leave it
for next week. We got to introduce all
the cars that I've gotten as well. You
know, I don't think I've done a
full-blown Bugatti intro on the car. The
new G Wagon Manhart that I got. And I
just added another thing to the
addition. And we're going to incorporate
Jordan. We're going to incorporate
Jordan next week 100%. See if he can do
donuts with the stick which would be
super sick.
So, with that being said, trade update,
right? So, as you guys can see or as you
guys just saw,
the account last left off at $90,000.
It pisses me off just a little bit, not
a lot, that we could have actually
closed this trade in a lot more profit.
So, this trade we closed out impulsively
because of the move. But if we would
have simply continued to set and forget
this trade throughout the whole entire
week, we would have ended off with a one
to nine risk to reward. We would have
literally closed at about $200,000 on
this one position right here. And you
know, it is what it is. We hit the goal
for the week. Can't get greedy. And I'm
not I'm glad I didn't even I didn't even
see this happen because I would have
just felt some type of way. But the
experience let me get away from the
charts, get busy with other things so I
could only focus on what matters and
it's a different opportunity. Don't just
get FOMO and want to chase this trade.
So, AUDUSD
currently on the market. So, taking it
back to AUDUSD,
we actually ended up having a reaction
from the take profit point that we
wanted to. Then price on the last 4
hours of Friday, it ended up having a
ginormous bearish candlestick rejection,
left head right shoulder, retest of the
neckline, retest of the EMA, beautiful
move to the downside. Next week, we're
going to be interested in taking this
trade continuously to the downside so we
will be on the lookout for that. You see
it right now on the daily time frame,
beautiful left head right shoulder.
Beautiful break of the neckline, we're
going to now wait for a retest to pretty
much head to the downside. And clearly
you can see last time we were up at this
resistance, kind of created a little
left head and shoulders, then we had a
ginormous push. This is a way stronger
formation in the same exact zone. We can
expect a continuation pattern from here.
And the AUDJPY, we ended up having the
move exactly how we anticipated, but we
never got the retest how we wanted to.
Even though we technically did, we did
have the break, we did have the retest,
just wasn't as clean as I wanted to.
GBPNZD avoided this last to perfection
due to what I explained.
Um, and even though it does look like
this, I would this is a loss that I
would have taken. Like, I would have
taken this loss probably
consecutively for 2 years. And I would
always ask myself, why am I losing? Why
am I losing?
And it, you know, after you get punched
in the face a bunch of times, you have
to realize to put your defense up or to
kind of get out of the way. This is
letting me know when to get out the way
from the markets because it is simply
not the right time to trade. Even though
yes, it does look good, and if this were
to happen on a Monday or Tuesday, I'd
take it all day. But towards the end of
the week, I'm not going to take it
because I just know that the odds of it
playing out aren't as high as if it were
to be a Monday or a Tuesday. But the
only way you could actually get that is
by experience. So, don't, you know,
break your head or, you know, hit
yourself if you're making these
mistakes. I made them for a really long
time. Now, I just kept going and
learning from it and avoiding it now.
So, my win rate and my probability is
not because of how many winning trades I
take, it's because of how many losing
trades just like this I avoid. Remember
that. So, GBPNZD, we'll update next week
exactly what we're going to be
interested in doing with it. USDJPY,
we already explained it. GBPJPY had the
break and retest to sell. And NZDJPY
never really gave us the entry. So,
every single one of these trades I
literally share every single Sunday with
my students. I get on a live call with
them where I'm sharing with them every
single one of these trades, where I'm
looking to get in, where I'm looking to
get out, why am I and why am I not. I'm
literally on a live call with you guys,
answering your questions, and giving you
the trades that I'm taking in this 100
to the mill series. If you click the
link in the description below, I have a
video for you that explains to you what
the Cent Per Gain strategy is and how I
do this every single week. If you join
the Cent Per Gain community, you get my
whole entire course, you get my private
and Discord community where students are
literally discussing these trades all
the time. Look, let me actually show you
guys my Discord community because I feel
like I never really ever show you guys
this.
So, look, this is my Discord community.
This is a little bit of an insight. So,
you can see people here ask questions
regarding the challenge. We have the
actual trading community itself, which
is obviously fully private. And then we
have the success room where students are
posting, you know, profits and
withdrawals. Like, this guy, why Cent
Per Gain Army is worth it. Um, here you
can see this is last week's profits. He
says he's learned a lot. This guy makes
He turned $2,000 into $9,000 with the
trades that I literally just explained
that just happened right now.
Um, this guy right here made $16,000 on
his funded account on FTMO. Like,
literally, this is all the profit and
loss from the students. So, this is all
If you guys click the link in the
description below, join the community,
you're going to be able to see me live
every single Sunday, get access to my
course, get access to my community, and
my psychology series. If you're not part
of the Cent Per Gain community,
honestly, you're missing out. So, next
week is going to be week 10 of us trying
to turn $100 into a million. And the
goal is to turn these $90,000 into now
$180,000,
which truthfully, if we get a nice 1 to
4 risk reward, we can turn the 90 to
half a mill, and we're done in 2 weeks,
baby. When I'm done with this challenge,
I'm out. So,
join the Cent Per Gain community before
I bounce.